

Taeyoung Kim

AUTONOMOUS DRIVING · ROBOTICS SW ENGINEER

340, Mokdongseo-ro, Yangcheon-gu, Seoul, 08089, Republic of Korea

 $\square \ (+82) \ 10-9686-8177 \quad | \quad \blacksquare \ tyoung96@naver.com \quad | \quad \ref{thm:start} \ \ taeyoung96.github.io/ \quad | \quad \blacksquare \ Taeyoung96$

"Nothing ventured, nothing gained."

Summary

This is Taeyoung Kim, who wants to become an autonomous driving or robotics SW engineer. My research interests are Computer Vision and Sensor Fusion. I like to take on challenging tasks and I like to grow up with my colleagues around me. That's why I record and share what I did on my Github or Technical Blog. I would like to participate in changing the world with advanced science and technology.

Research Interests

Computer Vision Object Detection, Segmentation, Depth Estimation

Sensor Fusion Combination of camera, lidar, and radar

Education

Kwang Woon University

Seoul, S.Korea

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022 (Expected)

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

• Current GPA: 4.07 / 4.50, Current Major GPA: 4.50 / 4.50

• Club: BARAM (Robotics Academic Group) - [2020 Staff], DAISY (English Conversation Club) - [2019 Spring President]

Work Experience _

KIST(Korea Institute of Science and Technology)

Seoul, S.Korea

STUDENT INTERN (ADVISOR : DR. KANGGUN KIM)

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- Research on Monocular Depth Estimation
- Participated in KIST disinfect robot (Al Disinfection Robot) project

Image Process System Lab @Kwang Woon Univ

Seoul, S.Korea

Undergraduate Lab Intern (Advisor : Prof. Donggyu Sim)

• Research on Image Processing based on Deep learning

Participated in seminars related to Deep Learning and Image Processing

Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2020

Honors & Awards

AWARDS

2020.11	Dean's List, KwangWoon University	Seoul, S.Korea
2020.9	5th Place on B-track , Korea Health Datathon 2020	Seoul, S.Korea
2019.10	Dean's List, KwangWoon University	Seoul, S.Korea

Honors

	2020-2	National Science and Engineering Undergraudate Scholarship (Full fuition Scholarship),	Seoul, S.Korea
	2020-2	Korea Student Aid Foundation	Seoul, S.Norea
	2020-1	National Science and Engineering Undergraudate Scholarship (Full tuition Scholarship),	Seoul, S.Korea
		Korea Student Aid Foundation	
	2019-2	Full tuition Scholarship, KwangWoon University	Seoul, S.Korea

Skills

Programming C++/C, Python, JAVA, Matlab **Framework** Pytorch, Tensorflow, Keras

DevOps Git, Docker, ROS **Languages** Korean, English

Extracurricular Activity

Technical Blogs Github blog

• Writing some posts about lecture summary, paper review, some tips for developments.

• To share what I have studied with others and to remember it longer.

Monocular Depth Estimation with ORB-SLAM2

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group)

PERSONAL TOY PROJECT

Sep. 2020 - Nov. 2020

May. 2020 - Present

Aug. 2020

• I was curious about the performance of the recent depth estimation model.

• Tused 'Monocular Depth Estimation with Transfer Learning pretrained MobileNetV2' model and applied to ORB-SLAM2, and compared with ORB-SLAM2(Monocular mode), ORB-SLAM2(RGB-D mode)

KCCV 2020 Korea computer vision society

PARTICIPANT • Participated to know about the trend of Computer Vision

Using deep learning for data analysis and image processing (Basic)

Korea open source software

STUDENTS

WRITERS

Jul. 2020

• Studied lectures which is related to the using Deep learning framework(Keras)

Runner Alarm System based on Deep Learning

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group)

PERSONAL TOY PROJECT Apr. 2020 - Jun. 2020 • I want to distinguish between walking children and running children with an object detection model.

• When children are running for an amount of time, a beep sounds.